{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335228719","data":{"timestamp":" 947335228719"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" c7006085-966c-4908-a588-da13c7a638ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-f-n"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335234138","data":{"timestamp":" 947335234137"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" c7006085-966c-4908-a588-da13c7a638ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_t-n-b"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335237776","data":{"timestamp":" 947335237776"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" c7006085-966c-4908-a588-da13c7a638ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_d-s-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335242403","data":{"timestamp":" 947335242403"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" c7006085-966c-4908-a588-da13c7a638ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-d-e"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335246528","data":{"timestamp":" 947335246528"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" c7006085-966c-4908-a588-da13c7a638ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_w-y-e"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335250892","data":{"timestamp":" 947335250892"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" c7006085-966c-4908-a588-da13c7a638ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-d-j"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335255349","data":{"timestamp":" 947335255349"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" c7006085-966c-4908-a588-da13c7a638ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_z-i-g"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335259202","data":{"timestamp":" 947335259202"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" c7006085-966c-4908-a588-da13c7a638ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_g-n-h"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335263651","data":{"timestamp":" 947335263651"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" c7006085-966c-4908-a588-da13c7a638ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_i-ch-r"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335267196","data":{"timestamp":" 947335267196"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" c7006085-966c-4908-a588-da13c7a638ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_j-h-t"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335271033","data":{"timestamp":" 947335271033"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" c7006085-966c-4908-a588-da13c7a638ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_j-k-o"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335274740","data":{"timestamp":" 947335274740"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" c7006085-966c-4908-a588-da13c7a638ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_w-l-f"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335278439","data":{"timestamp":" 947335278439"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" c7006085-966c-4908-a588-da13c7a638ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-n-s"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335283571","data":{"timestamp":" 947335283571"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" c7006085-966c-4908-a588-da13c7a638ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_b-h-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335288984","data":{"timestamp":" 947335288984"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" c7006085-966c-4908-a588-da13c7a638ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_w-o-y"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335295198","data":{"timestamp":" 947335295197"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" c7006085-966c-4908-a588-da13c7a638ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_m-p-s"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335299477","data":{"timestamp":" 947335299477"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" c7006085-966c-4908-a588-da13c7a638ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_v-r-d"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335303697","data":{"timestamp":" 947335303697"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" c7006085-966c-4908-a588-da13c7a638ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_i-h-s"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335308490","data":{"timestamp":" 947335308490"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" c7006085-966c-4908-a588-da13c7a638ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_t-r-z"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335312187","data":{"timestamp":" 947335312187"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" c7006085-966c-4908-a588-da13c7a638ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_u-i-h"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335316261","data":{"timestamp":" 947335316261"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" c7006085-966c-4908-a588-da13c7a638ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_v-i-k"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335319987","data":{"timestamp":" 947335319987"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" c7006085-966c-4908-a588-da13c7a638ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_d-w-m"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335323831","data":{"timestamp":" 947335323831"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" c7006085-966c-4908-a588-da13c7a638ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_y_n-y-f"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335327234","data":{"timestamp":" 947335327233"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" c7006085-966c-4908-a588-da13c7a638ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335333013","data":{"timestamp":" 947335333011"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" c7006085-966c-4908-a588-da13c7a638ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335352857","data":{"timestamp":" 947335352856"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" 553f9ffe-a77a-4a93-8dd7-fb872f57c892"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335354982","data":{"timestamp":" 947335354982"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" 553f9ffe-a77a-4a93-8dd7-fb872f57c892"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335357058","data":{"timestamp":" 947335357057"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" 553f9ffe-a77a-4a93-8dd7-fb872f57c892"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335360184","data":{"timestamp":" 947335360183"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" 553f9ffe-a77a-4a93-8dd7-fb872f57c892"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335362385","data":{"timestamp":" 947335362385"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" 553f9ffe-a77a-4a93-8dd7-fb872f57c892"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335364581","data":{"timestamp":" 947335364580"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" 553f9ffe-a77a-4a93-8dd7-fb872f57c892"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335367416","data":{"timestamp":" 947335367416"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" 553f9ffe-a77a-4a93-8dd7-fb872f57c892"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335369590","data":{"timestamp":" 947335369590"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" 553f9ffe-a77a-4a93-8dd7-fb872f57c892"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335371740","data":{"timestamp":" 947335371739"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" 553f9ffe-a77a-4a93-8dd7-fb872f57c892"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335374975","data":{"timestamp":" 947335374975"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" 553f9ffe-a77a-4a93-8dd7-fb872f57c892"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335377051","data":{"timestamp":" 947335377050"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" 553f9ffe-a77a-4a93-8dd7-fb872f57c892"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335379159","data":{"timestamp":" 947335379158"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" 553f9ffe-a77a-4a93-8dd7-fb872f57c892"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335382174","data":{"timestamp":" 947335382173"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" 553f9ffe-a77a-4a93-8dd7-fb872f57c892"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335384433","data":{"timestamp":" 947335384432"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" 553f9ffe-a77a-4a93-8dd7-fb872f57c892"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335386680","data":{"timestamp":" 947335386679"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" 553f9ffe-a77a-4a93-8dd7-fb872f57c892"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335389721","data":{"timestamp":" 947335389721"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" 553f9ffe-a77a-4a93-8dd7-fb872f57c892"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335392041","data":{"timestamp":" 947335392041"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" 553f9ffe-a77a-4a93-8dd7-fb872f57c892"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335394366","data":{"timestamp":" 947335394365"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" 553f9ffe-a77a-4a93-8dd7-fb872f57c892"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fagio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAGIO"," userResponse":" FAGIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335397473","data":{"timestamp":" 947335397472"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" 553f9ffe-a77a-4a93-8dd7-fb872f57c892"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335399590","data":{"timestamp":" 947335399590"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" 553f9ffe-a77a-4a93-8dd7-fb872f57c892"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335401715","data":{"timestamp":" 947335401714"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" 553f9ffe-a77a-4a93-8dd7-fb872f57c892"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335404909","data":{"timestamp":" 947335404909"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" 553f9ffe-a77a-4a93-8dd7-fb872f57c892"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335407113","data":{"timestamp":" 947335407112"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" 553f9ffe-a77a-4a93-8dd7-fb872f57c892"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335409307","data":{"timestamp":" 947335409307"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" 553f9ffe-a77a-4a93-8dd7-fb872f57c892"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hunywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335412454","data":{"timestamp":" 947335412453"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" 553f9ffe-a77a-4a93-8dd7-fb872f57c892"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335414893","data":{"timestamp":" 947335414892"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" 553f9ffe-a77a-4a93-8dd7-fb872f57c892"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335417307","data":{"timestamp":" 947335417306"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" 553f9ffe-a77a-4a93-8dd7-fb872f57c892"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Imara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMARA"," userResponse":" IMARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335420519","data":{"timestamp":" 947335420518"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" 553f9ffe-a77a-4a93-8dd7-fb872f57c892"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335422763","data":{"timestamp":" 947335422762"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" 553f9ffe-a77a-4a93-8dd7-fb872f57c892"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335425049","data":{"timestamp":" 947335425048"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" 553f9ffe-a77a-4a93-8dd7-fb872f57c892"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335428027","data":{"timestamp":" 947335428026"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" 553f9ffe-a77a-4a93-8dd7-fb872f57c892"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335430263","data":{"timestamp":" 947335430262"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" 553f9ffe-a77a-4a93-8dd7-fb872f57c892"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335432513","data":{"timestamp":" 947335432512"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" 553f9ffe-a77a-4a93-8dd7-fb872f57c892"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335435547","data":{"timestamp":" 947335435546"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" 553f9ffe-a77a-4a93-8dd7-fb872f57c892"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335437934","data":{"timestamp":" 947335437934"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" 553f9ffe-a77a-4a93-8dd7-fb872f57c892"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335440245","data":{"timestamp":" 947335440245"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" 553f9ffe-a77a-4a93-8dd7-fb872f57c892"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335443291","data":{"timestamp":" 947335443291"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" 553f9ffe-a77a-4a93-8dd7-fb872f57c892"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335445610","data":{"timestamp":" 947335445610"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" 553f9ffe-a77a-4a93-8dd7-fb872f57c892"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335447937","data":{"timestamp":" 947335447937"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" 553f9ffe-a77a-4a93-8dd7-fb872f57c892"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335450819","data":{"timestamp":" 947335450819"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" 553f9ffe-a77a-4a93-8dd7-fb872f57c892"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335453060","data":{"timestamp":" 947335453060"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" 553f9ffe-a77a-4a93-8dd7-fb872f57c892"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335455259","data":{"timestamp":" 947335455258"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" 553f9ffe-a77a-4a93-8dd7-fb872f57c892"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335457138","data":{"timestamp":" 947335457138"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" 553f9ffe-a77a-4a93-8dd7-fb872f57c892"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335473120","data":{"timestamp":" 947335473120"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" af49029d-0f42-4380-99b7-89b11a4bfc11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335473493","data":{"timestamp":" 947335473493"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" af49029d-0f42-4380-99b7-89b11a4bfc11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335473976","data":{"timestamp":" 947335473976"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" af49029d-0f42-4380-99b7-89b11a4bfc11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335474320","data":{"timestamp":" 947335474320"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" af49029d-0f42-4380-99b7-89b11a4bfc11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335474723","data":{"timestamp":" 947335474722"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" af49029d-0f42-4380-99b7-89b11a4bfc11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335475196","data":{"timestamp":" 947335475196"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" af49029d-0f42-4380-99b7-89b11a4bfc11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335475421","data":{"timestamp":" 947335475421"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" af49029d-0f42-4380-99b7-89b11a4bfc11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335478590","data":{"timestamp":" 947335478590"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" af49029d-0f42-4380-99b7-89b11a4bfc11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335478629","data":{"timestamp":" 947335478629"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" af49029d-0f42-4380-99b7-89b11a4bfc11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335479353","data":{"timestamp":" 947335479352"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" af49029d-0f42-4380-99b7-89b11a4bfc11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335479759","data":{"timestamp":" 947335479758"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" af49029d-0f42-4380-99b7-89b11a4bfc11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335480066","data":{"timestamp":" 947335480065"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" af49029d-0f42-4380-99b7-89b11a4bfc11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335480269","data":{"timestamp":" 947335480269"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" af49029d-0f42-4380-99b7-89b11a4bfc11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335480462","data":{"timestamp":" 947335480462"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" af49029d-0f42-4380-99b7-89b11a4bfc11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335480776","data":{"timestamp":" 947335480776"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" af49029d-0f42-4380-99b7-89b11a4bfc11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335481001","data":{"timestamp":" 947335481001"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" af49029d-0f42-4380-99b7-89b11a4bfc11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335484121","data":{"timestamp":" 947335484121"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" af49029d-0f42-4380-99b7-89b11a4bfc11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335484525","data":{"timestamp":" 947335484524"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" af49029d-0f42-4380-99b7-89b11a4bfc11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335487021","data":{"timestamp":" 947335487021"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" af49029d-0f42-4380-99b7-89b11a4bfc11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335487224","data":{"timestamp":" 947335487224"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" af49029d-0f42-4380-99b7-89b11a4bfc11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335487427","data":{"timestamp":" 947335487427"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" af49029d-0f42-4380-99b7-89b11a4bfc11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335490872","data":{"timestamp":" 947335490871"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" af49029d-0f42-4380-99b7-89b11a4bfc11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335494538","data":{"timestamp":" 947335494538"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" af49029d-0f42-4380-99b7-89b11a4bfc11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335495561","data":{"timestamp":" 947335495561"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" af49029d-0f42-4380-99b7-89b11a4bfc11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335498212","data":{"timestamp":" 947335498212"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" af49029d-0f42-4380-99b7-89b11a4bfc11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335498585","data":{"timestamp":" 947335498584"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" af49029d-0f42-4380-99b7-89b11a4bfc11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335499068","data":{"timestamp":" 947335499068"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" af49029d-0f42-4380-99b7-89b11a4bfc11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335499411","data":{"timestamp":" 947335499411"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" af49029d-0f42-4380-99b7-89b11a4bfc11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335499814","data":{"timestamp":" 947335499814"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" af49029d-0f42-4380-99b7-89b11a4bfc11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335500289","data":{"timestamp":" 947335500288"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" af49029d-0f42-4380-99b7-89b11a4bfc11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335500512","data":{"timestamp":" 947335500512"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" af49029d-0f42-4380-99b7-89b11a4bfc11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335503703","data":{"timestamp":" 947335503703"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" af49029d-0f42-4380-99b7-89b11a4bfc11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335503738","data":{"timestamp":" 947335503738"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" af49029d-0f42-4380-99b7-89b11a4bfc11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335504451","data":{"timestamp":" 947335504451"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" af49029d-0f42-4380-99b7-89b11a4bfc11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335504845","data":{"timestamp":" 947335504845"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" af49029d-0f42-4380-99b7-89b11a4bfc11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335505138","data":{"timestamp":" 947335505138"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" af49029d-0f42-4380-99b7-89b11a4bfc11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335505342","data":{"timestamp":" 947335505342"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" af49029d-0f42-4380-99b7-89b11a4bfc11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335505537","data":{"timestamp":" 947335505536"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" af49029d-0f42-4380-99b7-89b11a4bfc11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335505851","data":{"timestamp":" 947335505850"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" af49029d-0f42-4380-99b7-89b11a4bfc11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335506074","data":{"timestamp":" 947335506074"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" af49029d-0f42-4380-99b7-89b11a4bfc11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335508792","data":{"timestamp":" 947335508792"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" af49029d-0f42-4380-99b7-89b11a4bfc11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947335508858","data":{"timestamp":" 947335508858"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_154015"," gameId":" af49029d-0f42-4380-99b7-89b11a4bfc11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}